THE TRIPLETS OF BELLEVILLE
佳麗村三姐妹
We apologize for this interruption...
我們為節目中斷 致上最深的歉意
Is the movie over?
電影做完了嗎？
Don't you want to tell grandma?
你不跟奶奶說嗎？
We now continue with a musical interlude.
現在繼續插播一段音樂
In this 17th stage of the Tour de France
環法自行車大賽 已經進入第17段賽程
the pack, the machine of muscles and steel, finally gets going.
這群鋼鐵般的鐵騎健兒 終於就要啟程
But before the rubber tests the overheated paving-stones of Marseille,
在抵達馬賽 燙人的石面大街之前
these young lads still have many obstacles to face.
這些年輕小伙子 還得面對許多挑戰
And a fantastic escape by the yellow jersey,
有位黃衫選手脫穎而出
who devours Klaut and Glutman of the canned food factory from Frankfurt.
他從法蘭克福就盯上了 罐頭隊的克勞特和格魯曼
They'll have a hard time catching up
要追上可不太容易
on the spot where they already failed miserably last year,
去年他們就是在此落敗
When they really had to bite the bullet.
他們真的是吃到苦頭了
How admirable this fierce endurance is
令人讚賞的驚人毅力
On the face of this great eagle.
完全呈現在這張臉上
The very top lies at an altitude of 1912 metres,
最高點有海拔1912公尺
the horrible Ventoux, an impressive scenery
令人生懼的馮杜山 景色壯麗
of white desert, under a burning sun.
熾熱陽光下 白色沙漠盡收眼底
They climb standing on the pedals,
選手們踩著踏板上山
Constantly watching their gear ratio, It is hell.
還得保持速度不變 真是太折磨人了
But before they reach the finish,
但在抵達終點前
they work themselves into a sweat,
他們只會付出每一滴汗水
and leave behind that musky smell,
什麼也不想
That supporters know so well.
車迷們是最清楚不過了
The pack sink into oblivion.
我們看看後面的隊伍
For some the bell already sounds And they give up.
有些選手拉響了 放棄的車鈴
Those who can not really pound the pedals,
他們無力再踩踏板
lose pace, fall behind,
失速落後
vanish into nothingness.
沒人再注意他們
Together with a dazzling speed comes the liberating descent
進入下坡後 選手們加快速度
to Marseille.
就要進入馬賽了
Keep going, my boy!
加油，年輕人！
Insurance company "The Pigeon" gives away a whole week’s free insurance
信鴿保險公司 將贈送一星期的免費保險
for the best sprinter.
給獲勝的選手
Yes, that's right, for free, for his bicycle.
沒錯，自行車的免費保險
My box! That's my box! Give me back my box!
盒子！我的盒子！ 把盒子還我！
Is that your dog?
這是妳的狗嗎？
I don’t believe it! The nerve!
真不敢相信！ 神經病！
She now has my box and the dog!
她搶走了我的狗和盒子！
Here, stuff this!
看這裡！
Dried tadpoles
蝌蚪乾
Get out.
出去
And now: The triplets of Belleville.
現在為各位介紹 佳麗村三姐妹
Another racer’s grave discovered. Third in two months’ time
又在墓園發現運動員 兩個月來的第三位受害者！
Sinister details
現場佈滿不吉利的東西
Investigation got stuck
調查陷入困境
French Mafia denies everything!
法國黑幫否認涉案！
BELLEVILLE Thank you for your visit - Goodbye
佳麗村 - 感謝您的光臨 - 再見
Is the movie over?
電影做完了嗎？
Don't you want to tell grandma?
你不跟奶奶說嗎？ 是電影做完了嗎？
It's finished, grandma.
電影做完了 奶奶
For my parents.
獻給我的父母